<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>News on NWERC 2022</title>
    <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/</link>
    <description>Recent content in News on NWERC 2022</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>W.I.S.V. &lsquo;Christiaan Huygens&#39;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>NWERC 2023 date announced</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-2023-date/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 08 Jun 2023 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-2023-date/</guid>
      <description>The 2023 edition of the NWERC will be held from the 24th to the 26th of November. More information can be found on the 2023 NWERC website.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spectator contest</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/spectator-contest/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 24 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/spectator-contest/</guid>
      <description>There will be a spectator contest hosted on spectator.nwerc.eu. Here you can self-register your team! The contest will start at 10:30 CET on Sunday (November 27th, 2022). This is half an hour later than the start of the real contest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Livestream URLs</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/livestreams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/livestreams/</guid>
      <description>The URLs for the livestreams have already been created, and can be found here:
Opening Ceremony Livestream Test Session and Team Interviews Livestream Contest Livestream Award Ceremony Livestream </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Activity page updated</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/activities-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Nov 2022 15:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/activities-updated/</guid>
      <description>We have updated the activities page. There, you can find an overview of what activities are availble for November 26th. You can indicate your interest for an activity in the form within the last information mail which was sent out on Tuesday the 22nd of November. Contact us if you have not gotten this e-mail.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advice, Hints, and General Information from the NWERC Jury</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/new-jury-advice/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/new-jury-advice/</guid>
      <description>The NWERC Jury have prepared a document containing general advice. It has information on input and output formatting and how submissions are judged during a contest, as well as tips about interactive problems. It can be found under Jury Advice in the top menu. This advice will be available to you during a contest as a PDF.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Registration completed</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/registration-complete/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Nov 2022 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/registration-complete/</guid>
      <description>The registration for NWERC 2022 has been completed. There are a total of 140 teams from 61 institutions. A list of all teams can be found on the teams page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Sleeping at TU Delft Campus</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/sleeping-on-campus/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Oct 2022 12:30:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/sleeping-on-campus/</guid>
      <description>We provide 150 sleeping places for free at the TU Delft Campus in a sport hall. This requires you to bring your own sleeping mats/bags and breakfast. You will be able to shower on the site. Entry to the sleeping hall is possible on the following dates:
Friday night to Saturday morning: from 00:00 until 07:00 Saturday night to Sunday morning: from 22:00 until 07:00 Note that the sports halls will be used during the day, so you will need to clear away your sleeping bags before 07:00 on both days.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Call for Runners for NWERC 2022</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/runner/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/runner/</guid>
      <description>For the 2022 edition of NWERC, we are looking for volunteers (runners) to help during the weekend. The NWERC is from Friday the
25th of November to Sunday the 27th of November. The job of a runner includes helping set up the contest hall, joining participants in activities, and bringing balloons and prints during the contest. If you want to volunteer as runner, you can fill in the form here.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>New pages added</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/website-updated/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 09:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/website-updated/</guid>
      <description>We have added several new pages with information in preparation of the contest.
Systems Rules Registration Location We also invite coaches to join the NWERC slack. More information on the contact page.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subregional Overview</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/subregionals/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2022 08:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/subregionals/</guid>
      <description>Every year, four subregionals are held to train and select teams for the NWERC. The dates for these events are:
GCPC (Germany): June 25 NCPC (Nordic region): October 8 BAPC (Benelux region): October 22 UKIEPC (UK and Ireland): October 29 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Save the date, NWERC 2022 edition</title>
      <link>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/date-official/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Apr 2022 12:52:27 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://2022.nwerc.eu/news/date-official/</guid>
      <description>The 2022 edition of the Northwestern Europe Regional Contest (NWERC) will be held on the 25th of November until the 27th of November 2022. The contest will be held on the campus of the Delft University of Technology. More details on the location and exact schedule will be posted later.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
