<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Nwerc 2024 on NWERC 2024</title><link>https://2024.nwerc.eu/tags/nwerc-2024/</link><description>Recent content in Nwerc 2024 on NWERC 2024</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>W.I.S.V. &lsquo;Christiaan Huygens&rsquo;</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:14:00 +0100</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://2024.nwerc.eu/tags/nwerc-2024/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Conclusion of NWERC</title><link>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-conclusion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Nov 2024 00:14:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-conclusion/</guid><description>&lt;p>The NWERC 2024 has concluded. Congratulations to the champion, &lt;strong>Kindergarten Timelimit&lt;/strong>, from Karlsruhe Institute of Technology.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>The following teams have qualified for the ICPC World Finals 2025:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Kindergarten Timelimit&lt;/strong> (Karlsruhe Institute of Technology)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Segfault go BRRRR&lt;/strong> (Delft University of Technology)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Seems to be O(k!)&lt;/strong> (Hasso Plattner Institute)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>Additionally, the following teams have qualified for the &lt;a href="https://euc.icpc.global">Europe Championship 2025 in Porto&lt;/a>:&lt;/p>
&lt;ol>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Kindergarten Timelimit&lt;/strong> (Karlsruhe Institute of Technology)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Segfault go BRRRR&lt;/strong> (Delft University of Technology)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Seems to be O(k!)&lt;/strong> (Hasso Plattner Institute)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Pizza Driven Development&lt;/strong> (Aarhus University)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>placeholder&lt;/strong> (University of Oxford)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Oecher&lt;/strong> (RWTH Aachen University)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Bubblegum Bitset&lt;/strong> (University of Tartu)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Friday Volleyball&lt;/strong> (University of Amsterdam)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>TriTUMvirate&lt;/strong> (Technische Universität München)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Team Biem&lt;/strong> (Utrecht University)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>Unity&lt;/strong> (University of Cambridge)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>🥶&lt;/strong> (Chalmers University of Technology)&lt;/li>
&lt;li>&lt;strong>addicted (òvó)&lt;/strong> (Saarland University)&lt;/li>
&lt;/ol>
&lt;p>We apologize for mistakenly announcing during the Award Ceremony that team &lt;strong>Test2&lt;/strong> (Oxford) had qualified for the EUC. Due to the rule that only one team per institution can advance, the team &lt;strong>addicted (òvó)&lt;/strong> from Saarland University has qualified instead.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Online Spectator Contest</title><link>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/spectator-announcement/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 09:00:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/spectator-announcement/</guid><description>&lt;p>There will be an online spectator contest again this year.
The main contest will start at 10:30 CET on Sunday (November 24th, 2024).
This is half an hour later than the start of the real contest.
The test session on Saturday will also be available on the online spectator website.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>You can register at &lt;a href="https://spectator.nwerc.eu/">https://spectator.nwerc.eu/&lt;/a> once the website is live, this will probably be on Friday.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Last Information</title><link>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-last-info/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 00:14:00 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-last-info/</guid><description>&lt;p>The 2024 ICPC Northwestern Europe Regional Contest will take place this weekend, and we hope that you and your team are
prepared for this great event. Please check the pages for the &lt;a href="https://2024.nwerc.eu/systems">latest system information&lt;/a> and the
&lt;a href="https://2024.nwerc.eu/schedule">schedule&lt;/a>.&lt;/p>
&lt;p>We want to remind you of the following:&lt;/p>
&lt;ul>
&lt;li>The contest machines will be desktops. We do not allow you to replace the keyboard or mouse.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>During the contest, you are only allowed to use your Team Reference Document (TRD) as reference material. You may
bring three identical copies of the document per team, clearly marked with the university and team name. For
specifications on the TRD, please check &lt;a href="https://2024.nwerc.eu/booklet">the online booklet&lt;/a>. Your TRD should be handed in at registration. It is not
possible to print the TRD at the contest site.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>This year there will be no water bottle in the goody bag. We advise you to bring your own refillable water bottle. The
water bottles can be filled at all water taps. The water from Dutch water taps can be drunk safely.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>We will not be providing perishable cups this year. You will receive a mug in your goody bag to use during the
weekend. If you wish, you can also bring your own travel mug.&lt;/li>
&lt;li>Please be sure to bring everything you want to use during the contest, including mascots and snacks, on Saturday to
the test session. You are not allowed to bring anything on Sunday, except unmodified liquid containers.&lt;/li>
&lt;/ul>
&lt;p>The program booklet will be online this year. It contains a lot of useful information about the contest and the
companies making this contest possible. You can read the booklet &lt;a href="https://2024.nwerc.eu/booklet">here&lt;/a>.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Announcing the NWERC 2024 lit(e) date</title><link>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Mar 2024 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://2024.nwerc.eu/news/nwerc-data/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are happy to announce that the 2024 edition of the Northwestern Europe Regional Contest (NWERC) will be held from the
22nd until the 24th of November. The contest will be hosted this year again by the Delft University of Technology. We are
looking forward to welcoming 70 teams to compete for slots for the 2024 ICPC World Finals. More information will be
published in the coming months on this website.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>